PRIVACY POLICY

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address or other contact information.

Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information, which is publicly available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with certain services given under the Site, you must create an account ("Account") and provide us with your email address and password that you will use for your Account ("Requested Details").

We may request additional Personal Information in the future.

We use Personal Information for the following purposes: to identify and authenticate your access to dewbag Services that you are authorized to access, to provide you with the services provided under the Site, to improve our services to you and to contact you.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Our site's Form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address, telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code/pin code). Certain information, such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.

In addition to this, information about your viewing trends is collected in order to assess the consumer trends. We also may obtain and collect information about you when you log into our site through third party social networking websites.

In the future, if you decide to avail any services we offer, then we will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address ("Financial Information"). Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. We do not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with the service.

COOKIES

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Websites.

"Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information, which is targeted to your interests.

EXTERNAL LINKS ON WEBSITE

The Offering may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. dewbag Web Services may have no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than dewbag Web Services.

You acknowledge and agree that dewbag Web Services is not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources

You acknowledge and agree that dewbag Web Services is not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources.

OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use customer contact information from the form to send you information about dewbag Web Services. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud. Dewbag Web Services will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.

CONFIDENTIALITY

You further acknowledge that the Offering may contain information which is designated confidential by dewbag Web Services and that you shall not disclose such information without dewbag Web Services' prior written consent. Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your email address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Websites. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

For Payment: We may use and share the User information with reliable and reputed third party payment gateway to whom we are associated in order to ensure swift and comfortable payment mechanism for the User. The third-party payment gateway and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information and your credit/debit card details will be handled by these providers. Once you leave our store's website or are redirected to a third party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website's Terms of Service.

External Service Providers: There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our Websites. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their private policy.

Other Corporate Entities: We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that we and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs).

Law and Order: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

YOUR USE OF OTHER MEMBERS INFORMATION

As a user of the Service you will have access to other users' personal information. You agree to use this information solely for sharing and communicating on the site. The Company and its users shall not tolerate spam of any kind. Accounts suspected of causing spam will be deleted immediately and such users shall not be allowed to register again. You are thus not permitted to contact any user of the Service via e-mail, marketing messages or other kinds of spam without receiving their prior consent. Please feel free to report any users you suspect of using the Service as a platform for spamming by contacting customer support.

You understand that all information (such as data files, written text, computer software, or images) which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of, the Offering are the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated.

ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You can change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and profile.

To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support team. We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies.

Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

SECURITY

We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.

NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T & C AND PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. We will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on the Website.

You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this website immediately.

Terms Of Use

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SERVICE

1. Introduction

1.1) Your use of Dewbag Retail Pvt. Ltd. (henceforth dewbag.com) Product and Groceries. (referred to as the offering in this document and excluding any offering provided to you by dewbag.com under a separate written agreement) is subject to these terms, without prejudice to any additional terms which may be part of an agreement specific to the service you wish to avail of. Your agreement with dewbag.com will always include, at a minimum, the terms and conditions set out in this document.

1.2) dewbag.com does not sell its own products or services but acts as a link to other service - providers.

2. Accepting the Terms

2.1) dewbag.com shall interact with customers / clients through E-mail, Form on our website and Phone call, Skype or similar service. . By clicking a button or checkbox on a website. you accept and agree to the terms, where this option is made available to you by dewbag.com in the user interface for any offering.

2.2) In order to use the offering, you must first agree to the terms. You may not use the offering if you do not accept the terms.

3. Provision of the offering by dewbag.com

3.1) dewbag.com will attempt to continuously innovate in order to provide the best possible offering for its users. You acknowledge and agree that the form and nature of the offering which dewbag.com provides may change from time to time.

3.2) You acknowledge and agree that dewbag.com may stop (permanently or temporarily) providing the offering (or any features within the offering) to you or to users generally at dewbag.com's sole discretion.

3.3) You acknowledge and agree that while dewbag.com may not currently limit your use of the offering in any way, it may do so if that use hinders with the ability of dewbag.com to carry on its operations or the ability of other customers to use the offering.

3.4) The supply of the offering will only be subject to your making payments.

3.5) dewbag.com shall not be responsible for any loss or damage caused by a modification of the features, limitation of use of the offering or the discontinuation altogether thereof.

4. Pricing

4.1) All products listed in the dewbag.com site will be sold at a price either less than or equivalent to the Marginal Retail Price (MRP) of the product but not more than the MRP.

4.2) The products ordered by the customer will be sold at the same price as mentioned in the site at the time when the order is executed.

4.3) The listed price of the commodities are subject to change on regular basis as per the change in the market price.

5. Cancellation Policy

5.1) Customers can cancel any orders from dewbag.com at anytime upto the cutoff time by calling out customer service and dewbag.com will refund any payment already made by the customer for the order.

6. Return & Refund

6.1) Customer can return the product at the time of the delivery if the item is not as expected. The cost charged for the item will be refunded without any questions.

7. Colors of the product images and Description about products

7.1) The actual colors you see on the products or items, will depend on your monitor, we cannot guarantee or assure that your monitor's display of any color will be accurate. The images or description of the products in the dewbag.com will subject to change when ever there is a change in the product packing by the vendor or manufacturer.

8. Promotions, Discounts and Coupons

8.1) Dewbag.com reserves the right to offer the discounts/promotional offers to any dewbag.com customer of its choice and shall not be held liable to any customer for not offering the same.

8.2) The discounts/offers have been made available at the sole discretion of dewbag.com and are subject to change.

8.3) Dewbag.com at its sole discretion, may at any time discontinue the discounts/offers without assigning any reasons or without any prior intimation whatsoever.

9. Links To Third Party Sites:

9.1) The Website may contain links to other websites ("other URL or Linked Sites").The Linked Sites are not under the control of www.dewbag.com and not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site.

9.2) Dewbag.com is not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by you from any Linked Site.

9.3) Dewbag.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by dewbag.com or the Website of the Linked Sites or any association with its operators or owners including the legal heirs or assigns thereof. The users are requested to verify the accuracy of all information on their own before undertaking any reliance on such information.

10. Use of the offering by you

10.1) In order to access certain offering, you may be required to provide information about yourself as part of the registration process for the service, or for your continued use of the offering. You agree that any registration information you give to dewbag.com will always be accurate, correct and up to date.

10.2) dewbag.com can share customer/ client information with no one, except Employees and agents (for eg. You may share addresses with delivery agents), Any company which you acquire / acquires you and To the Government or law enforcement agencies (if officially requested or required by Order, Notification, Statute or Court Order).

10.3) You agree to use the offering only for your personal, non-commercial use and for purposes that are permitted by (a) the terms and (b) any applicable law, regulation or guidelines.

10.4) You agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of the offering by any means other than through the interface that is provided by dewbag.com, unless you have been specifically allowed to do so in a separate agreement with dewbag.com

You specifically agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of the offering through any automated means (including through the use of scripts or web crawlers).

10.5) You agree that you will not engage in any activity that interferes with or disrupts the offering (or the servers and networks which are connected to the offering).

10.6) Unless you have been specifically permitted to do so in a separate agreement with dewbag.com, you agree that you will not reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, trade or resell the offering for any purpose.

10.7) You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that dewbag.com has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any breach of your obligations under the Terms and for the consequences (including any loss or damage which dewbag.com may suffer) of any such breach.

10.8) You are solely responsible for the comments or opinions expressed on the site. Dewbag is not responsible for, and disclaims any and all liability for the content of comments written by contributors.

11. Your passwords and account security

11.1) You agree and understand that you are responsible to dewbag.com and to third parties for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with any account you use to access the offering.

You will be solely responsible for all activities that occur under your account.

11.2) dewbag.com will take due care to ensure the confidentiality of your credentials. You agree and acknowledge that in the very unlikely event of your credentials becoming known to a third party on account of an intrusion into dewbag.com database, dewbag.com shall not be made liable for the resulting damages.

11.3) If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password or of your account, you agree to notify the concerned official at dewbag.com immediately.

12. Content in the offering

12.1) You understand that all information (such as data files, written text, computer software, or images) which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of, the offering are the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated.

12.2) You should be aware that content presented to you as part of the offering, including but not limited to advertisements and promotional material of dewbag.com or other companies, is protected by intellectual property rights which are owned by dewbag.com, or the sponsors or advertisers who provide that content to dewbag.com (or by other persons or companies on their behalf). You may not modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, copy or create derivative work based on this content (either in whole or in part) unless you have been specifically told that you may do so by dewbag.com or by the owners of that content, in a separate agreement. Any content being disseminated using dewbag.com's sales network or the product, service or platform may be pre-screened, reviewed, flagged, filtered, modified or simply refused or removed. Any spam or pornographic material and / or any illegal content will be immediately deleted and we reserve the right to take appropriate legal action.

12.3) You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that dewbag.com has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any content that you create, transmit or display while using the offering or for the consequences of your actions (including any loss or damage which dewbag.com may suffer) by doing so.

12.4) You understand that by using the offering you may be exposed to content of other users that you may find offensive, indecent or objectionable and that, in this respect, you use the offering at your own risk. dewbag.com shall not be made responsible for any repugnant content circulated on its offering by other users. The user generated content is thoroughly verified by site administrator, before it is made available to other users.

12.5) On noticing any such content, it is your duty to bring it to the attention of dewbag.com officials immediately, who will take due care to delete it from the offering.

13. Intellectual Property rights

13.1) You acknowledge and agree that dewbag.com (or dewbag.com's licensors) owns all legal right, title and interest in and to the offering, including any intellectual property rights which subsist in the offering (whether those rights happen to be registered or not, and wherever in the world those rights may exist). You further acknowledge that the offering may contain information which is designated confidential by dewbag.com and that you shall not disclose such information without dewbag.com's prior written consent.

13.2) Unless dewbag.com has otherwise agreed in writing, nothing in the terms gives you a right to use any of dewbag.com's trade names, trademarks, service marks, logos, domain names, and other distinctive brand features. You additionally agree that in using the offering, you will not use any trade mark, service mark, trade name, logo of any company or organization in a way that is likely or intended to cause confusion about the owner or authorized user of such marks, names or logos.

13.3) dewbag.com acknowledges and agrees that it obtains no right, title or interest from you (or your licensors) under these terms in or to any content that you submit, post, transmit or display on, or through, the offering, including any intellectual property rights which subsist in that content (whether those rights happen to be registered or not, and wherever in the world those rights may exist). Unless you have agreed otherwise in writing with dewbag.com, you agree that you are responsible for protecting and enforcing those rights and that dewbag.com has no obligation to do so on your behalf.

14. License from dewbag.com

14.1) dewbag.com gives you a license to use the software provided to you by dewbag.com as part of the offering as provided to you by dewbag.com. This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the offering as provided by dewbag.com, in the manner permitted by these terms.

14.2) You are not entitled to commercially exploit, either directly or by sale, or transfer commercially or profit from the offering and products.

14.3) You may not (and you may not permit anyone else to) copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, decompile or otherwise attempt to extract the source code of the software or any part thereof.

14.4) The payment mode for the offering may be either fixed, invoice based or recurring. The payment cycle will be in the manner decided at the discretion of dewbag.com.

15. Ending your relationship with dewbag.com

15.1) The Terms will continue to apply until terminated by either you or dewbag.com as set out below.

15.2) dewbag.com may at any time, terminate its legal agreement with you if:

A. you have breached any provision of the terms (or have acted in manner which clearly shows that you do not intend to, or are unable to comply with the provisions of the terms); or
B. dewbag.com is required to do so by law (for example, where the provision of the offering to you is, or becomes, unlawful)

15.3) When these terms come to an end, all of the legal rights, obligations and liabilities that you and dewbag.com are subject to in relation to the obligation to maintain confidentiality or such other legal rights, obligations and liabilities which are expressed to continue indefinitely, shall be unaffected by this cessation.

16. EXCLUSION OF WARRANTIES

16.1) YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE OFFERING IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE OFFERING ARE PROVIDED AS IS AND AS AVAILABLE.

16.2) IN PARTICULAR, dewbag.com DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT TO YOU THAT:

A. YOUR USE OF THE OFFERING WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS,
B. YOUR USE OF THE OFFERING WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE OR FREE FROM ERROR, INCLUDING SPECIFICALLY FROM SERVER DOWNTIME,
C. ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE OFFERING WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, AND

16.3) ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE OFFERING IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND dewbag.com WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR OTHER DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.

16.4) NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM dewbag.com OR THROUGH OR FROM THE OFFERING SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THE TERMS.

16.5) dewbag.com FURTHER EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

17. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

17.1) SUBJECT TO OVERALL PROVISION IN CLAUSE 11 ABOVE, YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT dewbag.com SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR:

A. ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, HOWEVER CAUSED AND UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY. THIS SHALL INCLUDE, BUT NOT BE LIMITED TO, ANY LOSS OF PROFIT (WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY), ANY LOSS OF GOODWILL OR BUSINESS REPUTATION, ANY LOSS OF DATA SUFFERED, COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR OFFERING, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS;
B. ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OR DAMAGE AS A RESULT OF:

i. ANY CHANGES WHICH dewbag.com MAY MAKE TO THE OFFERING, OR FOR ANY PERMANENT OR TEMPORARY CESSATION IN THE PROVISION OF THE OFFERING (OR ANY FEATURES WITHIN THE OFFERING);
ii. THE DELETION OF, CORRUPTION OF, OR FAILURE TO STORE, ANY CONTENT AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS DATA MAINTAINED OR TRANSMITTED BY OR THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE OFFERING;
iii. YOUR FAILURE TO PROVIDE dewbag.com WITH ACCURATE ACCOUNT INFORMATION;
iv. YOUR FAILURE TO KEEP YOUR PASSWORD OR ACCOUNT DETAILS SECURE AND CONFIDENTIAL; 

18. Changes to the Terms

18.1) dewbag.com may make changes to the terms from time to time. The same will be communicated to you, on the website of 2 A, without prior intimation to you. Your continued use of the offering will indicate your acceptance of the modified terms. When these changes are made, dewbag.com shall make the amended copy of the terms available in an accessible location.

18.2) You understand and agree that if you use the offering after the date on which the terms have changed, or after the date by which you have to respond as per these terms has passed, dewbag.com will treat your use as acceptance of the amended terms.

19. General legal terms

19.1) Sometimes when you use the offering, you may (as a result of, or through your use of the offering) use a service or download a piece of software, or purchase goods, which are provided by another person or company. Your use of these other offering, software or goods may be subject to separate terms between you and the company or person concerned.

19.2) The terms constitute the legal agreement between you and dewbag.com and govern your use of the offering, but without prejudice to any additional terms which may be part of an agreement specific to the service you wish to avail of. (but excluding any offering which dewbag.com may provide to you under a separate written agreement), and completely replace any prior agreements between you and dewbag.com in relation to the offering.

19.3) You agree that if dewbag.com does not exercise or enforce any legal right or remedy which is contained in the terms (or which dewbag.com has the benefit of under any applicable law), this will not be taken to be a formal waiver of dewbag.com's rights and that those rights or remedies will still be available to dewbag.com.

19.4) If any court of law, having the jurisdiction to decide on this matter, rules that any provision of these terms is invalid, then that provision will be removed from the terms without affecting the rest of the terms. The remaining provisions of the terms will continue to be valid and enforceable.

19.5) The terms, and your relationship with dewbag.com under the terms, shall be governed by the laws of India and be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts at Bangalore. The High Court of judicature at Bangalore alone shall have the jurisdiction.

You and dewbag.com agree that any dispute will be referred to arbitration, with the arbitral panel consisting of three arbitrators, one arbitrator being chosen by each party and a third being jointly appointed by the two arbitrators so chosen.